<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Emotions on SerializingMe</title>
    <link>https://www.serializing.me/tags/emotions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emotions on SerializingMe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:06:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.serializing.me/tags/emotions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Freedom and Solitude</title>
      <link>https://www.serializing.me/2022/11/16/freedom-and-solitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.serializing.me/2022/11/16/freedom-and-solitude/</guid>
      <description>The freedom of not having to account for someone else&#39;s needs and wants, has the cost of solitude.
Silva, Duarte. 2022  Image via Pexels @ Pixabay</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facts and Alternative Realities</title>
      <link>https://www.serializing.me/2018/07/21/facts-and-alternative-realities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.serializing.me/2018/07/21/facts-and-alternative-realities/</guid>
      <description>(...) simply insisted we prove that the Queen didn’t do it — that is, demanding a refutation of wild speculation to prove fact, rather than seeking out the evidence first. This proof-by-negation is akin to fastidiously believing in the tooth fairy simply because no one has seen proof that the tooth fairy doesn’t exist. That is noxious thinking — and, (...), it’s exactly the kind of aggressive, close-minded speculation that fuels fake news, Trumpian rhetoric, and political divisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://www.serializing.me/2015/04/25/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 11:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.serializing.me/2015/04/25/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>The man of modern industrial society thinks, repeatedly, that he can replace the loss of intimacy through external mechanisms. This belief is reinforced by a series of activities that promise you hope and happiness, but that really only leaves you the insipid taste of an even greater disappointment.
Bender, Erich. Helga. Wiesbaden (Germany): Falken-Verlang, 1968  In a world where many strive to find instant happiness and gratification in one nighters, through Facebook likes, Twitter retweets and the ramp for limelight that YouTube views are known for, this quote from Erich F.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
